For love. For honor. For mankind.
Armageddon is a action, thriller, science fiction film directed by Michael Bay.
When an asteroid threatens to collide with Earth, NASA honcho Dan Truman determines the
only way to stop it is to drill into its surface and detonate a nuclear bomb.
This leads him to renowned driller Harry Stamper, who agrees to helm the dangerous
space mission provided he can bring along his own hotshot crew.
Among them is the cocksure A.J.
who Harry thinks isn't good enough for his daughter,
until the mission proves otherwise.
Harry S. Stamper, played by Bruce Willis.
Dan Truman, played by Billy Bob Thornton.
A.J. Frost, played by Ben Affleck.
Grace Stamper, played by Liv Tyler.
Chick, played by Will Patton.
Rockhound, played by Steve Buscemi.
Armageddon is a 1998 American science fiction disaster film directed
by Michael Bay and  co-produced by Jerry Bruckheimer.
The film follows a group of blue-collar deep-core drillers sent by NASA to destroy a
gigantic asteroid, which is the size of Texas, on a collision course with Earth.
It stars an ensemble cast including Bruce Willis with Billy Bob Thornton, Liv Tyler, Ben Affleck, Will
Patton, Peter Stormare, Keith David, Owen Wilson, William Fichtner and Steve Buscemi.
The film released on July 1, 1998 by Buena Vista Pictures
through its Touchstone Pictures label.
Despite receiving mixed reviews from critics, Armageddon was a commercial success, grossing $553.7 million worldwide against a $140 million
budget, becoming the highest-grossing film of 1998, and the highest-grossing film to be released by Touchstone Pictures.
The film explores themes of daughter, race against time,
space marine, moon, washington dc, usa.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.